http://www.needlepoint.com/pages/privacy-policy

HomePromotions The Plum Stitchery Trunk ShowRebecca Wood Trunk ShowSale ItemsShop New Arrivals
$58.00
FeaturedNew ArrivalsThe Plum Stitchery Trunk ShowRebecca Wood Trunk ShowBest SellersIn Stock CanvasesCanvases with Stitch Guides IncludedNeedlepoint KitsSale Canvases, Kits, and AccessoriesOnline Needlepoint ClassesGift CardsAll ProductsShop Canvases by CategoryShop Canvases by ArtistShop ThreadsShop AccessoriesView All CollectionsNeedlepoint by CategoryView All CategoriesChristmasOrnamentsAnimalsBabies & ChildrenBeachCloset CutiesColleges & UniversitiesFloralsGeometrics & PatternsHolidaysHouses & Key FobsLandscapesMakeablesPeopleSigns & SayingsTransportationWeddings & EngagementsNeedle Points Rewards ProgramGalleryOnline ClassesRetreat Fall RetreatElizabeth Bradley WeekendResources Finishing InformationFinishing Deadlines & CostsGeneral FinishingBelt FinishingStocking FinishingThread InformationThreads We Carry in Our StoreThread Options for CanvasesTips & Tricks for Using ThreadsLearnNew to NeedlepointTake Your Stitching to the Next LevelHelpful VideosThis is Needlepoint BlogTips on Couching20 Finishing InspirationsPantone Color of the YearNeedlepoint for BeginnersTips for Stitching a StockingThe History of Needlepoint.Com!View All PostsNeedle Points Rewards ProgramContact Us
Free US Shipping on Orders $200+
Navigate
Cart
Search
Home
Canvases
Online Classes
Kits
View All Artists
Check out our favorite new artists!
Back
Artist
Technique Classes
Ribbonwork Classes
Collections
Videos
Live Zoom Class Calendar
All Online Classes
Intro to Decorative Stitches
Just Bead It!
Perfectly Tailored Stitches
Turkey Work
Tricky Stitches
Santa's Beard Part I
Santa's Beard Part II
Openwork Backgrounds
Haunted Halloween Stitches
Frosty Stitches
Mary’s Whimsical Stitches-Volume Two
Metallic Scissors-Why you need a pair!
Meet Paige from Blue Ridge Stitchery
View All Blog Posts
How to Needlepoint
Take Your Stitching to the Next Level
Helpful Videos
Helpful Videos
Privacy Policy & Terms of Service
This privacy policy sets out how Needlepoint.Com uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. Needlepoint.Com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 17th of June 2013.
We may collect the following information:
Name
Contact information including email address and phone number
Demographic information such as postcode and interests
What we do with the information we gather:
We use this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service:
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file that asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting such sites, and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following way:
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to us at 3811 Hillsborough Street, Raleigh, NC 27607.
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
TERMS OF SERVICE
Welcome to Needlepoint.Com! Come in and look around! Continue on and while using this website, you are agreeing to comply with and be bound by the our terms and conditions of use, which together with our privacy policy govern Needlepoint.Com’s relationship with you in relation to this website. The term ‘Needlepoint.Com’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is 3811 Hillsborough Street, Raleigh, NC 27607. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website. The use of this website is subject to the following terms of use:
The content of the pages of this website is for your general information and use only. It is subject to change without notice.
Neither we nor any third parties provide any warranty or guarantee as to the accuracy, timeliness, performance, completeness or suitability of the information and materials found or offered on this website for any particular purpose. Such information and materials may contain inaccuracies or errors and we expressly exclude liability for any such inaccuracies or errors to the fullest extent permitted by law.
Your use of any information or materials on this website is entirely at your own risk, which we are not liable. It is your own responsibility to ensure that any products, services or information available through this website meet your specific requirements.
This website contains material which is owned by or licensed to us. This material includes, but is not limited to, the design, layout, look, appearance and graphics. Reproduction is prohibited other than in accordance with the copyright notice, which forms part of these terms and conditions.
All trade marks reproduced in this website which are not the property of, or licensed to, the operator are acknowledged on the website.
Unauthorized use of this website may give rise to a claim for damages and/or be a criminal offence.
From time to time this website may also include links to other websites. These links are provided for your convenience to provide further information. They do not signify that we endorse the website(s). We have no responsibility for the content of the linked website(s).
Your use of this website and any dispute arising out of such use of the website is subject to the laws of the United States of America.
Home
/ Privacy Policy & Terms of Service
